Guide to the Edie Windsor and Thea Spyer Papers MSS.642
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III. Activism, 1969-2024; 20.50 Linear Feet in 28 manuscript boxes, 2 small flat boxes, 3 oversize flat boxes, and 3 flat-file folders; 1,080 Megabytes in 718 computer files
  - Subseries III.A. Events and Appearances, 1969, 1981-2022; 12 Linear Feet in 16 manuscript boxes, 4 oversized flat boxes, and 2 flat-file folders.; 834.34 Megabytes in 432 computer files
    This series documents Edie Windsor and Thea Spyer's involvement in a wide range of events and appearances primarily organized by LGBTQ+ and allied organizations from the 1980s to the 2010s. In the earlier years, Windsor and Spyer often attended events as supporters or community participants. As their visibility grew, particularly following their 2007 marriage, the couple was increasingly recognized for their contributions to LGBTQ+ advocacy. After the 2013 United States v. Windsor Supreme Court case decision, Windsor's event appearances increased as she suddenly became a well-known public figure in her 80s. Her rigorous schedule of events which are represented in this subseries is centered on honoring her achievements, celebrating her public advocacy, or highlighting her cultural significance. Towards the end of Windsor's life she was accompanied by her spouse Judith Kasen-Windsor, who is also active in the LGBTQ+ community. Files dated after Windsor's death document events attended by Judith, who honored and carried on Windsor's legacy through her own activism.
    The majority of event and appearance files date from the 1980s though 2020s and typically include programs, schedules, invitations, speech text, press clippings, correspondence, publicity materials, print and digital photographs, and digital video event recordings.
    Several of these events within the subseries span over multiple years, including the New York City Gay Pride Parade and the SAGE Awards and Dinner Gala–two organizations that were deeply important to both women. Other events of note include the East End Women for the Arts' off-Broadway show Taking Liberties; the first National Lesbian Conference (1991); and The Edie Windsor and Thea Spyer Foundation Exhibit and Fundraiser from 2021.
    Material within this subseries is arranged in chronological order.
    - March on Washington Vietnam War Protest -- Photographs and Slides, November 15, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Art Exhibit Installation -- Photographs, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - NYC Gay Pride Day and Parade -- Slide Images, June 28, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - The East End Women for the Arts -- Event Programs and Meeting Notes, 1982-1993 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - The East End Women for the Arts' Off-Broadway Show Taking Liberties, March 30-31, 1984
      - Work Notebook (Box 34, Folder 19-20)
      - Photographs, Slides, and Negatives (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - NYC Gay Pride Parade Lavender Line -- Photographs, June 1985 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Annual Senior Action in a Gay Environment (SAGE) Awards -- Photograph, December 1985 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - The Matrix Fundraiser -- Photographs, June 1986 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Reception at 5th Avenue Apartment -- Slide Images, November 1986 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Old Lesbians Organizing for Change (OLOC) Meeting -- Photographs, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - SAGE Strategic Planning Meeting -- Slide Images, March 1987 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - West Coast Old Lesbian Conference and Celebration, April 24-26, 1987
      - Notes, Program, Newsletters (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Photographs and Negatives (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - NYC Gay Pride Day and Parade (Windsor and Spyer, Grand Marshals), June 28, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Lambda's 15th Anniversary Celebration, May 8, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - West Coast Old Lesbian Conference and Celebration, August 4-6, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Meeting Including Edie and Group -- Photographs, circa 1980s (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - SAGE Dance Marathon (Windsor and Spyer Won), January 27, 1990
      - Schedules, Promotional Material, Instructions, Sponsor Material, Dance Number (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Photographs and Negatives (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - NYC Gay Pride Parade -- Photographs, June 21, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - EEGO Benson Raffle Party -- Photograph, June 1990 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - National Lesbian Conference (Atlanta, Georgia), April 24-28, 1991
      - Schedules, Clippings, Program, Correspondence, Notes (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Photographs and Negatives (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - NYC Gay Pride Parade -- Photographs, June 30, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - NYC Gay Pride Parade -- Photographs, June 28, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - The 1993 March on Washington for Lesbian, Gay and Bi Equal Rights and Liberation, April 23, 1993
      - Program Guide (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Photographs and Negatives (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - NYC Gay Pride Parade -- Photographs, June 27, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Memorial for Barbara Phelan, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Gay Games IV and Cultural Festival, June 16-25, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - 25th Anniversary of Stonewall Riots -- Photographs, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Goldfarb and Freeman Wedding (Windsor is Speaker), November 30, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - The Annual Uncommon Woman Garden Party and Summer Casino, 1999-2000 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force Foundation Creating Change Conference (SAGE and OLOC), November 9-13, 2000
      - Informational Material, Schedules, Notes, Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Photographs and Negatives (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - SAGE Event with Edie and Group -- Photograph, circa 2000-2006 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Old Queers Acting Up Event with SAGE -- Photographs, April 18, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - 10th Annual SAGE Awards, November 13, 2005
      - Promotional and Planning Material (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Digital Video Recording, FA_MSS_642_ER_26
    - Annual SAGE Awards -- Photographs, circa 2005-2006 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Empire State Pride -- New York City Marriage Ambassador Training, June 5-6, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Unknown Event with Edie and Group -- Photograph, June 11, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Outdoor Event with Edie and Thea -- Photograph, June 2006 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - 11th Annual SAGE Awards, October 30, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Human Rights Award Presentation to Dr. Barbara Rosen, circa 2006 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - SAGE Awards Dinner, 2007 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Event with Edie and Thea -- Photograph, January 2008 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - 5th Anniversary of the Passage of Canada's Civil Marriage Act Event -- Photographs, June 14, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Irish Arts Center Event -- Photographs, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - NYC Gay Pride Parade -- Photographs, June 28, 2009 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Hamptons Tea Dance -- Photographs, July 11, 2009 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Edie Posing with Group at Unknown Parade / Protest, November 4, 2009 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - 15th SAGE Awards and Gala, October 25, 2010
      - Planning Materials, Program, Invitation (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Lifetime Achievement Award Speakers Dorothy Sander, Karen Sauvign, and Edie Windsor Digital Video Recordings, FA_MSS_642_ER_3
      - Bless Bless Productions Video Montage for Edie -- Digital Video Recording, FA_MSS_642_ER_27
    - Speeches and Partial Speeches for Various Events, 2010-2017 (Box 36, Folder 1-4)
    - Marriage Equality New York Trailblazer Award Ceremony, May 19, 2011
      - Planning Materials, Program, Speech Text, Press Clipping (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Digital Photographs, FA_MSS_642_ER_9
    - EEGO Memorial Day Event Digital Photographs, May 30, 2011; FA_MSS_642_ER_7
    - ACLU Roger N. Baldwin Medal of Liberty Ceremony, June 6, 2011
      - Planning Material, Speech Text (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Digital Video Recording, FA_MSS_642_ER_28
    - New York City Council -- A Celebration of LGBT Pride, June 16, 2011
      - Program, Planning Correspondence, Proclamation Certificate (Box 36, Folder 7, Box 75, Folder 10)
      - Digital Images, FA_MSS_642_ER_10
    - ACLU at The Center Garden Party -- Digital Images, June 19, 2011; FA_MSS_642_ER_5
    - 25th Anniversary of the ACLU LGBT and AIDS Project, June 21, 2011
      - Invitation, Speech Text, Planning Material (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Digital Images, FA_MSS_642_ER_4
    - New York City Gay Pride Parade, June 26, 2011
      - Print Photograph (Box 67, Folder 24)
      - Digital Images, FA_MSS_642_ER_11
    - SAGE Announcement for Gay Pride Parades in Queens, Brooklyn, and Manhattan, June 2011 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Various Events at Pride Week with Windsor Attending, June 2011 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - SAGE Creating Change Conference, January 26, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - NOW Susan B. Anthony Award Ceremony, February 15, 2012
      - Planning Material, Program, Speech Text (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Digital Images, FA_MSS_642_ER_13
    - The Loft Annual Benefit Gala, March 10, 2012
      - Planning Material, Program (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Digital Images, FA_MSS_642_ER_15
    - Callen-Lorde Spring Fever Healthy Sexy Women Event, April 19, 2012
      - Speech Text, Planning and Promotional Material (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Digital Images, FA_MSS_642_ER_6
    - Congregation Rodeph Sholom LGBT Pride Shabbat, June 1, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Christine Quinn for Mayor Event, June 12, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - NYC Gay Pride Parade, June 24, 2012
      - Print Photographs (Box 67, Folder 25)
      - Digital Images, FA_MSS_642_ER_12
    - NewFest Visionary Award Ceremony, July 27, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Callen-Lorde Community Health Award Introduction for Recipient Paul Weiss, November 5, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Event with Edie and Roberta Kaplan -- Photograph, December 8, 2012 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - EEGO Outdoor Event with Edie and Roberta Kaplan -- Photographs, 2012 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - The National Conferences on LGBT Equality-Creating Change, 2012-2013 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Event at 5th Avenue Apartment with Edie, Frank, and Zach -- Photograph, circa 2012-2013 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Various Events with Edie and Others -- Photographs, circa 2012-2017 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - "We are All Edie" March, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - The Center Dinner, April 11, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - New York Times Magazine Question and Answer Document, April 19, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Cardozo School of Law Discussion and Dinner, April 23, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Family Equality Council Introduction of Roberta Kaplan, April 29, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Village Independent Democrats Annual Awards Celebration, May 2, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Long Island Gay and Lesbian Youth (LIGALY) 20th Anniversary Gala, May 10, 2013
      - Planning Material, Program (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Digital Images, FA_MSS_642_ER_8
    - NYU Presidential Medal Ceremony and Related, May 22, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 8, Box 74, Folder 5)
    - LGBT Pride Month at the White House, June 13, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - New York City Pride Parade, Grand Marshal, June 30, 2013
      - Notes, Correspondence, etc. (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Photographs by B. Proud (Box 67, Folder 30)
      - Oversized Photographic Prints (Flat-file-folder 5)
      - Digital Images, FA_MSS_642_ER_14
    - Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton & Garrison Reception and Video Interview Preparation Material, July 18, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - GLAD (Gay and Lesbian Advocates and Defenders) Summer Party in Provincetown, July 27, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Gay Pride Iceland, July 31, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Long Island Gay and Lesbian Youth (LIGALY) Center Opening, August 10, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - The Feminist Press at CUNY Annual Hamptons Cocktail Party, August 25, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - The LOFT's Anniversary Benefit Gala, September 7, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Congregation Beit Simchat Torah Kol Nidre Services, September 13, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC) Interview Event, September 13, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - New York Constitution Day Luncheon for the American Constitution Society for Law and Policy, September 17, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Esquire Magazine Interview, September 19, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Out Magazine Video Shoot, Photograph Shoot, Event, September-October 2013 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt Legacy Committee Trailblazer of Democracy Award Luncheon, October 2, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - New Yorker Festival -- "In Conversation: Edith Windsor with Ariel Levy", October 6, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force Celebration, October 8, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Stanford Marriage Equality Conference Panel, October 11-12, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - PFLAG (Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays) of New York City Awards Dinner, October 14, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - NYU Graduate School of Arts and Science Dean's Day Award Lunch, October 19, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - SAGE Awards Gala, October 21, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Williams Institute Fall Reception, November 7, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Time Magazine Photograph Shoot and Interview, November 11, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - American Spirit Award for Citizen Activism Event, November 13, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - The Center Lunches, October, November 2013 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - NPR Interview on The Takeaway, December 26, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Christine Quinn Mayoral Campaign Video Message, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Event with Edie and Others, circa 2013-2014 (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - Olivia Cruise Vacation and Appearances, December 28, 2013 - January 4, 2014
      - Schedules, etc. (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Photograph of Edie with Passengers (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - Edie's Out Women Summit Proposal, December 2013 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Edie Attending New York Liberty Basketball Game -- Photograph, circa 2013-2017 (Box 67, Folder 33)
    - List of Windsor's Awards for 2013-2014 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - "The Case That Changed History" with Roberta Kaplan, at the 92nd Street Y, January 7, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Queens Pride Winter Gala -- Photograph, January 2014 (Box 67, Folder 34)
    - Olivia Cruise Vacation and Appearance, February 2-8, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - France State Dinner at the White House Attended by Windsor and Julie Mulligan, February 11, 2014
      - Planning Correspondence, Press Clippings (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - Photographs (Box 67, Folder 35)
    - Congressman Jerry Nadler Reception, February 24, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - "A Conversation with Edie Windsor with Suzanne Goldberg" at Columbia University, February 28, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 17, Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Home Lifecare 80 Over 80 Celebration, March 5, 2014
      - Program, Press Clippings, Notes, Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Photographs (Box 67, Folder 36)
    - LeGAL Award Presentation to Mary Bonauto, March 20, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Opening Night of Terrance McNally's Broadway Show Mothers and Sons, March 24, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Night of a Thousand Gowns, March 29, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - NYU Alumni Luncheon for Eugene J. Keogh Award Presentation, April 24, 2014
      - Event Program, Ticket, Speech Text, Correspondence, Certificate (Box 38, Folder 22, Box 74, Folder 6)
      - Photographs (Box 67, Folder 37)
    - Brooklyn Community Pride Center Founders' Ball, April 24, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - GOAL (Gay Officers Action League) Awards Banquet, April 25, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - "Edie Windsor: Unlikely Activist" Temple University Events, April 26, 2014
      - Promotional and Planning Material (Box 39, Folder 2, Box 73)
      - Alumni Fellow Certificate (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Photographs of Edie with People (Box 67, Folder 38)
    - Equality Florida St. Petersburg Gala, May 1-4, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Transgender Legal Defense and Education Fund Benefit, May 19, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Johns Hopkins University Honorary Doctorate Given to Edie, May 22, 2014
      - Speech Text, Program, Correspondence, Press Clipping, Certificate (Box 39, Folder 5, Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Photographs (Box 67, Folder 39)
    - Homeless Youth Rally, June 2, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Huffington Post Interview with Roberta Kaplan, June 5, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Long Island Pride Parade (Edie, Grand Marshal), June 14, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Dinner / Dance of The Alliance, June 17, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - DNC LGBT Gala, June 17, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - ACLU Interview, June 21, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - USA Today Interview Questions and Answers, June 22, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - LOGO TV Trailblazers Award with Roberta Kaplan, June 23, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - World Pride Event in Toronto, Canada, June 25, 2014
      - Event Itinerary, Speech Text, Notes, Press Clippings (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Photographs (Box 67, Folder 40)
    - American Federation of Teachers Women's Rights Award Event, July 14, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Rebecca Seawright Fundraiser, August 7, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - PFLAG of New York City Lunch, September 15, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Westchester Jewish Community Services (WJCS) Center Lane Fundraiser, September 18, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - DNC LGBT Gala, September 27, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Florida Governor Rick Scott Video Script for Windsor Message, September 2014 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - MTV / LOGO Speaker Session, October 16, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - SAGE Awards Gala, October 20, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Ali Forney Event, October 24, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Point Foundation's David Mixner Show, Oh Hell No!, October 27, 2014
      - Correspondence, Notes, Promotional Material (Box 39, Folder 24)
      - Photographs (Box 67, Folder 41)
    - Visiting Nurse Service of New York Staff Retreat, October 30, 2014
      - Promotional Material, Registration Form (Box 39, Folder 25)
      - Photographs (Box 67, Folder 42)
    - Callen-Lorde Thea Spyer Center for Integrated Health Opening Announcement and Event Material, November 6, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 26, Box 70, Folder Unknown)
    - Women's Event, Fundraiser for The Center, November 15, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Callen-Lorde Community Health Awards, November 17, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - SAGE Women's Holiday Tea Hosted by Edie Windsor, December 7, 2014 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - ACLU Questions for Magazine Interview, 2014 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Amsterdam Pride Parade, 2014 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Event Press Clippings and Articles, 2014-2017 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - The Center Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, February 3, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - SAGE National LGBT Elder Housing Initiative Launch, February 3, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 5-6)
    - James Madison High School Wall of Distinction for Marjorie Ellen Sherwin, February 16, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - The Center Women's Luncheon, March 7, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art Women's History Celebration, March 9, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - GMHC Spring Gala, March 23, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - An Evening with B. Proud Event "First Comes Love: Portraits of Enduring LGBTQ Relationships", March 26, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Broadway Show Fun Home, Event, and Windsor Comments for Show Program, March 28, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - The Center Dinner and Cocktail Hour, April 2, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Callen-Lorde Spring Fever Event, April 9, 2015
      - Promotional Material, Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Photograph (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Lesbian and Gay Big Apple Corps and Symphonic Band New York State of Mind Award, April 11, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Equality Florida (EQFL) Lifetime Achievement Award to Rose Walton, May 29, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - SAGE Centers Event, June 12, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Marriage Equality Rally in Sheridan Square, June 16 and 26, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Human Rights Campaign Online Birthday Message with Windsor Image and Quote, June 2015 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Equality Forum Award and 50th Anniversary-LGBT Civil Rights Movement in Philadelphia, July 4, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Empire State Pride Agenda Hamptons Tea Dance -- Photograph, July 18, 2015 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - GLAD (Gay and Lesbian Advocates and Defenders) Annual Summer Party in Provincetown, July 25, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - IBM-LGBT Meeting, October 2, 2015 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Lesbians Who Tech Summit, October 2, 2015
      - Promotional Material, Stickers, Schedule, Press Release, Article (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Photograph (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Carol Movie Premiere, October 9, 2015 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Clare Coss Birthday Celebration, October 13, 2015 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - SAGE Awards and Gala, October 19, 2015
      - Program, Speech Draft, Press Clipping, Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Photographs (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Institute for Retired Professionals Presents: "Edith Windsor: An Unlikely Activist" -- Including Edie and Thea: A Very Long Engagement Film Viewing and Discussion, October 30, 2015 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Women's Event, Fundraiser for The Center, November 7, 2015 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Callen-Lorde Community Health Awards, November 9, 2015 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Out Magazine Top 100 Event Red Carpet, November 11, 2015 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - NYU Skirball Gala with Terrance McNally and Tom Kirdahy, November 16, 2015 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Geriatrics Patient Panel with Medical Students, November 18, 2015 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - PCYP (Peter Cicchino Youth Project) Event, November 19, 2015 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - St. Pat's for All Documentary Interview, November 24, 2015 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Congregation Beit Simchat Torah "Architects of the LGBTQ Movement Discussion Series with Roberta Kaplan", December 17, 2015 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Equality Florida Gala, 2015 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - History in the Making: A Grassroots Fights for Marriage Equality Documentary Film Poster, 2015 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Digital Images from 2015 Events, FA_MSS_642_ER_41
    - Brendan Fay Nomination for President's Award for Irish Community Support, by Windsor, 2015-2016 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Buzzfeed Interview Along with Roberta Kaplan, January 6, 2016 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Hamptons LGBT Center Donor Reception, February 11, 2016 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Terrance McNally Documentary Interview, February 15, 2016 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - New York Fashion Week Party for USO, February 17, 2016 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Lesbians Who Tech Summit, February 25, 2016 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Gay City News Impact Awards, March 3, 2016 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - St. Pat's For All Parade, March 6, 2016
      - Program, Press Clipping (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - Photograph (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Women's History Month Awards Ceremony, March 24, 2016 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Live Out Loud Young Trailblazers Gala, April 25, 2016
      - Program, Promotional Material, Speech Draft (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - Photograph (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Third Annual AMPA (American Military Partner Association) National Gala, May 7, 2016
      - Program, Speech Draft, Press Clipping, Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 26)
      - Photograph (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Twenty Summers Fundraiser for Hawthorne Barn in Provincetown, May 7, 2016 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Edie's Backyard BBQ, for LGBT Network's Hamptons Center in Sag Harbor, May 28, 2016 (Box 41, Folder 28)